A Finding Aid to the Lee Nordness business records and papers, circa 1931-1992 (bulk 1954-1984), in the Archives of American Art AAA.nordlee
Archives of American Art
- Nordness Gallery, Inc. and Lee Nordness Galleries Art Advisory Section, Inc., bulk 1958-1982; circa 1938-1992; Series 1; 67.8 Linear feet Boxes 1-67, 117-119
  - Project Files, 1952-1990; 1.3
    - Council House Collection, 1968-1984; 1952; 1.3.5
      - Checklist of Art Collection, circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 36)
      - Contract, Catalog, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - Contract, Wind Point Conference Center, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box 30, Folder 39-41)
      - Country Files, Argentina-Colombia, 1968-1980 (Box 30, Folder 42-56)
      - Country Files, Costa Rica-South Africa, 1970-1981; 1952 (Box 31, Folder 1-49)
      - Country Files, Spain-Venezuela, 1977-1980 (Box 32, Folder 1-10)
      - Country Index Cards, circa 1978 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Executives, International Travel, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Floor Plans for Council House, circa 1978 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - General Managers, 1977-1980 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Gift Books, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Graphic, 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Hague, Richard, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Insurance Claims, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Inventory, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Inventory, Insurance Values, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Inventory, Location, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Itinerary, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - Johnson, Samuel, 1979-1981 (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - The Johnson Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Jones, E.O., 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - Keland, Karen, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - Mathis, Emile, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - McIlvane, Edward, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous, 1977-1980 (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - Nelson Storage "In" Receipts, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - Parker, Mike, 1979-1982 (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Permissions, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - Photographs, Architectural, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 33)
      - Reports, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - Rohner, Rudy, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - Spinks, R.M., 1979-1982 (Box 32, Folder 36)
      - Straub, Richard, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 37)
      - Worth, Bob, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Metromedia (Mr. X) Art Collection, 1960s-1975; 1.3.6
      Found are materials documenting the development of the Metromedia (Mr. X) art collection. Nearly half of the materials are artist's files containing biographies, correspondence, and scattered clippings, exhibition materials, inventory records, and photographic materials. Many artists files are empty, but have notations about paintings written on the original folders. Also found is a scrapbook with photographs of artwork and publicity clippings; inventory cards; travel files, and an artwork inventory ledger. Many of the same artists are also found in subseries 1.2.
      - Artists (Box 32)
        - Al-Akhlaq, Zahoor, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 39-40)
        - Ali, Shakir, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 41)
        - Allen, Gary, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 42)
        - Anderson, Fred, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 43)
        - Andrews, Oliver, 1969-1973 (Box 32, Folder 44)
        - Arjunka, Pricha, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 45)
        - Arneson, Robert, circa 1968 (Box 32, Folder 46)
        - Aronson, David, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 47)
        - Aye, Mansur, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 48)
        - Azuma, Syoko, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 49)
        - Bacerra, Ralph, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 50)
        - Backstrand, Jay, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 51)
        - Bagier, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 52)
        - Bailey, Clayton, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 53)
        - Baldessari, John, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 54)
        - Battenburg, John, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 55)
        - Bauer, Fred, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 56)
        - Bauer, Patti, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 57)
        - Beall, Dennis, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 58)
        - Bechtle, Robert, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 59)
        - Becker, David H., 1963 (Box 32, Folder 60)
        - Bengston, Billy Al, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 61)
        - Benoit, Rigaud, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 62)
        - Benton, Fletcher, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 63)
        - Blaustein, Al, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 64)
        - Borge, Ralph, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 65)
        - Bottex, J.B., 1960s (Box 32, Folder 66)
        - Bottex, S.E., 1960s (Box 32, Folder 67)
        - Brannen, Patricia, 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 68)
        - Broderson, Robert M., 1965-1966 (Box 32, Folder 69)
        - Burton, Dennis, circa 1966 (Box 32, Folder 70)
        - Butler, E.P., 1960s (Box 32, Folder 71)
        - Butler, K.J., 1960s (Box 32, Folder 72)
        - Carroll, Robert, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 73)
        - Cartwright, Roy, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 74)
        - Casimer, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 75)
        - Cavat, Irma, 1962-1964 (Box 32, Folder 76)
        - Chabet, Roberto Rodriguez, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 77)
        - Chakraborty, Debdas, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 78)
        - Chambers, John, circa 1965 (Box 32, Folder 79)
        - Chantaveera, Supote, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 80)
        - Chen Ting-shih, circa 1965 (Box 32, Folder 81)
        - Chi-chung, Hu, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 82)
        - Chihuly, Dale, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 83)
        - Chowdhury, Qayyum, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 84)
        - Chuang Che, 1965-1970s (Box 32, Folder 85)
        - Colescott, Warrington, 1965-1973 (Box 32, Folder 86)
        - Collette, Francois, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 87)
        - Collie, Alberto, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 88)
        - Colquit, Clair, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 89)
        - Connor, Colin Arthur, 1966-1970 (Box 32, Folder 90)
        - Cooper, Michael, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 91)
        - Covington, Harrison, 1960s-1972 (Box 32, Folder 92)
      - Artists (Box 33)
        - Crisp, Darrell, circa 1967 (Box 33, Folder 1)
        - Crutchfield, William, 1967-1973 (Box 33, Folder 2)
        - D'Arista, Robert, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 3)
        - Dass, Amba, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 4)
        - Dimanche, André, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 5)
        - Dimanche, Rene, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 6)
        - DiMeo, Dominick, 1964-1973 (Box 33, Folder 7)
        - Dodd, Margaret, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 8)
        - Domoto, Hisao, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 9)
        - Duffaut, Pierre, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 10)
        - Dugal, Donald, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 11)
        - Dunn, Warren, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 12)
        - Eades, Luis, 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 13)
        - Eddy, Donald, 1969-1972 (Box 33, Folder 14)
        - Edge, Doug, circa 1969 (Box 33, Folder 15)
        - Edwards, Stanley, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 16)
        - Elrod, Bennie, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 17)
        - Epting, Marion A., circa 1969 (Box 33, Folder 18)
        - Evett, Philip John, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 19)
        - Fabert, Jacques, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 20)
        - Fakphol, Prayut, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 21)
        - Fellows, Jack, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 22)
        - Fievre, Yolande, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 23)
        - Fishbach, Kurt, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 24)
        - Flynn, Robert, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 25)
        - French, Stephen, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 26)
        - Friel, John, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 27)
        - Fritsch, John, circa 1965 (Box 33, Folder 28)
        - Fukui, Ryonosuke, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 29)
        - Fukushima, Hideko, circa 1963 (Box 33, Folder 30)
        - Funai, Carol, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 31)
        - Gallo, Frank, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 32)
        - Garner, R. Bert, 1960s-1971 (Box 33, Folder 33)
        - Gasowski, R.E., 1969 (Box 33, Folder 34)
        - Gilhooly, Dale, circa 1968 (Box 33, Folder 35)
        - Gill, Charles, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 36)
        - Goo, Gwen-Lin, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 37)
        - Gooch, Gerald, circa 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 38)
        - Goyer, George, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 39)
        - Green, Anthony, 1974; circa 1964 (Box 33, Folder 40)
        - Greenly, Colin, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 41)
        - Griffith, Jean, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 42)
        - Gronberg, Erik, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 43)
        - Guiga, Chacha, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 44)
        - Hack, Howard, 1963-1968 (Box 33, Folder 45)
        - Han, Hsing-ning, 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 46)
        - Hansen, Robert, circa 1962 (Box 33, Folder 47)
        - Harden, Marvin, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 48)
        - Harvey, Robert, 1964-1969 (Box 33, Folder 49)
        - Heald, Larry, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 50)
        - Hebald, Milton, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 51)
        - Henderson, Gil, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 52)
        - Heyboer, Anton, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 53)
        - Higby, Wayne, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 54)
        - Higgins, Wilfred, 1961-1964 (Box 33, Folder 55)
        - Hockney, David, 1965; 1968 (Box 33, Folder 56)
        - Hoe, Khoo Swee, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 57)
        - Holder, Tom, circa 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 58)
        - Holman, Art, 1960s-1970s (Box 33, Folder 59)
        - Holman, Charles, 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 60)
        - Holt, Martin, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 61)
        - Hopper, David, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 62)
        - Horiuchi, Paul, 1963; 1966 (Box 33, Folder 63)
        - Huig, Henk, circa 1963-1969 (Box 33, Folder 64)
        - Huisman, (Sepke), 1960s (Box 33, Folder 65)
        - Hultberg, Peter, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 66)
        - Hutchins, Alice, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 67)
        - Hyson, Jean, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 68)
        - Ikeda, Masuo, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 69)
        - Inaba, Katura, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 70)
        - Islam, Aminul, 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 71)
        - Izquierdo, Manuel, circa 1964 (Box 33, Folder 72)
        - Jackson, Richard, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 73)
        - Johanson, George, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 74)
        - Joo, Seah Kim, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 75)
        - Jung, Michael, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 76)
        - Kachadoorian, Zubel, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 77)
        - Kaji, Kiichi, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 78)
        - Kaufman, Glen, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 79)
        - Kelley, Chapman, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 80)
        - Kelly, Lee, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 81)
        - Kenney, Leo, 1973; 1964 (Box 33, Folder 82)
        - Khanna, Krishen, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 83)
        - Kienholz, Ed, 1969; circa 1962 (Box 33, Folder 84)
        - Kikuchi, Kozo, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 85)
        - Ko, Nomura, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 86)
        - Koblick, Freda, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 87)
        - Kosuth, John, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 88)
        - Kosuth, Joseph, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 89)
        - Kottler, Howard, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 90)
        - Krairiksh, Piriya, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 91)
        - Kumar, Ram and Ramachandran, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 92)
        - Kurelek, William, circa 1966 (Box 33, Folder 93)
        - Kuzma, Stephen, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 94)
        - Laochareon, Pravat, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 95)
        - Lazarevich, Emil, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 96)
        - Le Parc, Julio, 1960s-1973 (Box 33, Folder 97)
        - Lebrun, Rico, circa 1960s (Box 33, Folder 98)
        - Lehrer, Leonard, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 33, Folder 99)
        - Leichman, Seymour, 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 100)
        - Lennard, John, 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 101)
        - Lewis, Lucy, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 102)
        - Liautaud, Georges, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 103)
        - Lipofsky, Marvin, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 104)
        - Liu, Kuo-sung, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 105)
        - Lockhart, Robert, circa 1966 (Box 33, Folder 106)
        - Lomoe, Julie, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 107)
        - Lucassen, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 108)
        - Lui, Shou-kwan, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 109)
        - Lundin, Norman, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 110)
        - Manzella, David B., 1960s (Box 33, Folder 111)
        - Martinez, Florence, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 112)
        - Martorell, Antonio, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 113)
        - Mason, John, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 114)
        - Matsumoto, Hiroshi, circa 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 115)
        - McChesney, Robert Pearson, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 116)
        - McCormick, Patrick, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 117)
        - McLarty, Jack, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 118)
        - McNutt, Mary, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 119)
        - Mehta, Tyeb, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 120)
        - Meigs, Walter, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 121)
        - Meitzler, Neil, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 122)
        - Melchert, Jim, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 123)
        - Merkin, Richard, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 124)
        - Merlier, Pierre, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 125)
        - Mexile, Nicholas, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 126)
        - Middaugh, Robert, 1974; 1965 (Box 33, Folder 127)
        - Milant, Jean, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 128)
        - Miller, Clive B., 1965 (Box 33, Folder 129)
        - Mirza, Bashir, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 130)
        - Morehouse, William, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 131)
        - Moriguchi, Hirokaza, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 132)
        - Morita, Shiryu, 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 133)
        - Moses, Richard, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 134)
        - Moty, Joyce, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 135)
        - Murphy, John, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 136)
        - Myers, Frances, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 137)
        - Myers, Joel P., 1960s (Box 33, Folder 138)
        - Nathan, J. Swami, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 139)
        - Natzler, Gertrud and Otto, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 140)
        - Nichols, James, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 141)
        - Nimsamer, Chalood, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 142)
        - Nomura, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 143)
        - Norris, Ben, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 144)
        - Obin, Antoine, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 145)
        - Obin, Philomene, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 146)
        - Ohasi, Yutaka, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 147)
        - Ohno, Hidetaka, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 148)
        - O'Shea, Terry, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 149)
        - Oxley, Dick, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 150)
        - Oxtoby, David, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 151)
        - Parrott, Alice, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 152)
        - Paulson, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 153)
        - Pathanapiradej, Pira, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 154)
      - Artists (Box 34)
        - Pereira, Irene Rice, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Pérez, Vincent, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 2)
        - Pernish, Paul, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - Perry, Charles O., 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - Peterdi, Gabor, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 5)
        - Peters, Michael, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - Pierre, Fernand, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 7)
        - Ping-Shih, Chen, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 8)
        - Piotrowski, Ronald, circa 1964-1968 (Box 34, Folder 9)
        - Popovitch, Chris, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 10)
        - Prentiss, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 11)
        - Price, Kenneth, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 12)
        - Procktor, Patrick, circa 1966 (Box 34, Folder 13)
        - Radakovitch, Toza, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 14)
        - Ramachandran, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 15)
        - Rampolla, Frank, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 16)
        - Raueel, Roger, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 17)
        - Ray, Fong Chung, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 18)
        - Rhaye, Yves, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 19)
        - Rice, Jacquelyn, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 20)
        - Richardson, Samuel, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 21)
        - Romero, Luis, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 22)
        - Root, Ednah, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 23)
        - Rose, Tom, late 1960s (Box 34, Folder 24)
        - Rosenbaum, John, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 25)
        - Rossbach, Ed, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 26)
        - Roubadoux, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 27)
        - Royer, Victor, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 28)
        - Samant, Mohan, circa 1966 (Box 34, Folder 29)
        - Sanders, Jeff, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 30)
        - Sangawong, Pote, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 31)
        - Satomi, Beisanjin, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 32)
        - Scholder, Fritz, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 33)
        - Schwartz, June, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 34)
        - Sekimachi, Kay, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 35)
        - Seyle, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 36)
        - Shaih, Li-Fa, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 37)
        - Shaner, David, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 38)
        - Shaw, Kendall, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 39)
        - Shaw, Richard, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 40)
        - Shores, Ken, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 41)
        - Simpson, David, circa 1964 (Box 34, Folder 42)
        - Smith, Richard, circa 1966 (Box 34, Folder 43)
        - Snelgrove, Walter, 1964-1971 (Box 34, Folder 44)
        - Soldner, Paul, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 45)
        - Souza, Francis, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 46)
        - Sperry, Robert, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 47)
        - Spratt, Fred R., 1968 (Box 34, Folder 48)
        - Squeri, Robert, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 49)
        - Stark, Larry, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 50)
        - Stephane, Micius, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 51)
        - Strini, Robert, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 52)
        - Stuck, Jack, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 53)
        - Summers, Martin, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 54)
        - Taher, Abu, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 55)
        - Takai, Teiji, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 56)
        - Tanaka, Atsuko, circa 1964 (Box 34, Folder 57)
        - Teneau, Peter V., 1966 (Box 34, Folder 58)
        - Thomas, Alma, 1970-1973 (Box 34, Folder 59)
        - Thrall, Arthur, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 60)
        - Tift, Mary, 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 61)
        - Tomioka, Soichiro, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 62)
        - Trowell, E.J.L., 1960s (Box 34, Folder 63)
        - Truss, Ned, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 64)
        - Tujitani, Kazuko, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 65)
        - Underhill, William, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 66)
        - Upton, Michael John, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 67)
        - Usami, Keiji, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 68)
        - Utermohlen, William Charles, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 69)
        - Valein, Gerald, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 70)
        - Valentine, DeWain, 1968-1972 (Box 34, Folder 71)
        - Varming, Erik, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 72)
        - Vaughn, Michael, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 73)
        - Verburg, Jan, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 74)
        - Vital, Pauleus, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 75)
        - Voelz, Vernon, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 76)
        - Voulkos, Peter, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 77)
        - Wagner, Gordon, 1969-1971 (Box 34, Folder 78)
        - Wah, Yong Cheng, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 79)
        - Wallace, Jerome, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 80)
        - Walters, Mon, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 81)
        - Walton, William, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 82)
        - Washington, Timothy, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 83)
        - Wayne, James, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 84)
        - Weege, William, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 85)
        - Wells, Charles, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 86)
        - Wesley, John, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 87)
        - White, circa 1960s (Box 34, Folder 88)
        - White, Jack, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 89)
        - Williams, Hiram, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 90)
        - Wilson, Bryan, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 91)
        - Winter, Roger, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 92)
        - Wong-Uparaj, Damrong, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 93)
        - Wright, G. Alan, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 94)
        - Yee, Cheung, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 95)
        - Yen, Wu Tsai, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 96)
      - Artwork Ledger, 1962-circa 1969 (Box 34, Folder 97)
        Oversized material housed in Box 118, Folder 1
      - Bekins Van & Storage Co., 1969 (Box 34, Folder 98)
      - Biographies (Artists A-Z), 1966-1975 (Box 34, Folder 99-101)
      - Biographies (Artists), Requests for Information, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 102)
      - Birsh, Arthur, 1969-1973 (Box 34, Folder 103)
      - Burleson, Malcolm, 1968-1971 (Box 34, Folder 104)
      - Catuogno, Mario, 1968-1971 (Box 34, Folder 105)
      - Claims, 1965-1969 (Box 34, Folder 106)
      - Collection Scrapbook, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 107)
      - Collection Scrapbook, 1960s (Box 35, Folder 1-12)
      - Conlon, Barbara, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Galleries, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, John Kluge, 1962-1971 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1965-1974 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Customs, Statement of Originality, circa 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Customs and Shipping, 1963-1967 (Box 35, Folder 18-19)
      - Detroit - Mr. X, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Douris, Karen, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Etkin, George, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Exhibition Loans, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Expenses (1963), 1962-1964 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Expenses, Bills, 1963-1964 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - Inventory, 1964-1970 (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - Inventory, Mr. X (shoebox), 1962-circa 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Inventory Information, 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Metromedia West, 1966-1971 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Metromedia West Acquisitions, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Nameplates, 1964-1969 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Niepold, Robert, 1964-1969 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Parmenter, Kay, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Peterson, Pat, 1963-1967 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Publicity, Mr. X, 1961-1966 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Ratcliffe, Mary, 1966-1968 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Statements, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Travel Expenses, 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Travel Files, Bangkok-Washington, D.C., 1964-1967 (Box 36, Folder 13-29)
      - Wank, Adams and Slavin, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - Weber, Clements - Dick Geismar, 1965-1969 (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - Oversized Artwork Ledger, 1962-circa 1969 (Box 118, Folder 1)
        Oversized material from Box 34, Folder 102
    - Corporate Files, 1965-1977; 1.3.7
      Found in this sub-subseries is mostly correspondence to corporations to pitch ideas, much of which is related to the U.S. bicentennial. It appears as though most of the proposals were unsuccessful.
      - American Art by American Minorities, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - American Indian Art, 1968-1976 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Black Art, 1968-1976 (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
      - Corporate Art Councils, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Corporate Clippings, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Corporate Rejects, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Corporate Replies, 1965-1975 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Corporate Replies, Favorable, 1965; 1970 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Ethnic, 1970s (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Ford Motor Company, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Form Letters, 1970-1975 (Box 37, Folder 12-13)
      - Form Letters, Fortune 500, 1969-1971 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Fortune 500 Corporations Replies, 1965-1970 (Box 37, Folder 15-16)
      - Fountains for America, 1970-1977 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - IBM, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Ideas, 1962-1974 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Jazz, 1968-1976 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Jazz (Box 37)
        - ARBA, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 21)
        - CBS, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 22)
        - Classes, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 23)
        - Collective Black Artists, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 24)
        - Dance, 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 25)
        - Institute of Jazz Studies, 1970-1974 (Box 37, Folder 26-27)
        - Jazz Adventures, circa 1974 (Box 37, Folder 28)
        - Jazz Composers Orchestra Association, circa 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 29)
        - Jazz Interactions, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 30-31)
        - Jazzmobile, 1972; 1974 (Box 37, Folder 32)
        - New York Jazz Museum, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 33-34)
      - Jazz (Box 38)
        - New York Jazz Repertory Company, 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - Performers, 1974-1977 (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - Performers, Foreign, 1970s (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - Prospectus, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Records, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - Zenith, Artie Shaw, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - Zenith Radio Corporation, 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Museum of Black History, 1970; 1977 (Box 38, Folder 8)